<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoneyDiariesACTIVE Book Recommendations</title>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/MoneyDiariesACTIVE</link>
    <description>Monthly book recommendations from r/MoneyDiariesACTIVE</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:22:21 +0900</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Atmosphere by Taylor Jenkins Reid</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=xLH10AEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Atmosphere%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-06-03&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781529152975&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=xLH10AEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Atmosphere cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=xLH10AEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Atmosphere%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=xLH10AEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781529152975</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-06-03T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily Henry 4 Books Collection Set: Book Lovers, Beach Read, People We Meet on Vacation &amp; Happy Place by Emily Henry</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2022-04-13&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9798998881114&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Emily Henry 4 Books Collection Set: Book Lovers, Beach Read, People We Meet on Vacation &amp; Happy Place cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798998881114</guid>
      <dc:date>2022-04-13T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Sisters by Coco Mellors</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Blue+Sisters%2Binauthor:Coco+Mellors&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; From the Sunday Times bestselling author of Cleopatra and Frankenstein ﻿&#39;A stunning exploration of sisterhood and grief, addiction and recovery, pain and pleasure. Captivating&#39; TESS GUNTY &#39;In Blue Sisters, grief is rendered with gorgeous particularity&#39; RAVEN LEILANI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-05-21&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 384&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780008623012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Blue Sisters cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Blue+Sisters%2Binauthor:Coco+Mellors&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780008623012</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-05-21T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The God of the Woods by Liz Moore</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=9NHcEAAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; ONE OF THE NEW YORK TIMES’S NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2024 A NEW YORK TIMES BEST THRILLER OF 2024 A NEW YORK TIMES BEST CRIME NOVEL OF 2024 PEOPLE MAGAZINE’S #1 BOOK OF THE YEAR ONE OF NPR’S “BOOKS WE LOVE” 2024 ONE OF TIME MAGAZINE’S “100 MUST-READ BOOKS OF 2024” &quot;A long novel that at first is hard to put down. By page 200, impossible.&quot; —Stephen King “Extraordinary . . . Reminds me of Donna Tartt’s 1992 debut, The Secret History . . . I was so thoroughly submerged in a rich fictional world, that for hours I barely came up for air.” —Maureen Corrigan, Fresh Air, NPR “This expertly paced thriller …has the kineticism of a well-crafted miniseries.” —The New Yorker When a teenager vanishes from her Adirondack summer camp, two worlds collide Early morning, August 1975: a camp counselor discovers an empty bunk. Its occupant, Barbara Van Laar, has gone missing. Barbara isn’t just any thirteen-year-old: she’s the daughter of the family that owns the summer camp and employs most of the region’s residents. And this isn’t the first time a Van Laar child has disappeared. Barbara’s older brother similarly vanished fourteen years ago, never to be found. As a panicked search begins, a thrilling drama unfolds. Chasing down the layered secrets of the Van Laar family and the blue-collar community working in its shadow, Moore’s multi-threaded story invites readers into a rich and gripping dynasty of secrets and second chances. It is Liz Moore’s most ambitious and wide-reaching novel yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-07-02&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 497&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593418932&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=9NHcEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The God of the Woods cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=9NHcEAAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=9NHcEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593418932</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-07-02T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Dark Shore by Charlotte McConaghy</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=5wcAEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER • #1 AMAZON BEST BOOK OF THE YEAR SO FAR 2025 An ENTHRALLING new novel from the NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING author of Migrations and Once There Were Wolves &quot;A WILDLY TALENTED writer.&quot; ―Emily St. John Mandel “SPELLBINDING...Exceptionally imagined, thoroughly humane.” —Washington Post “Abounds with EVOCATIVE nature writing.” —The New York Times Book Review A family on a remote island. A mysterious woman washed ashore. A rising storm on the horizon. Dominic Salt and his three children are caretakers of Shearwater, a tiny island not far from Antarctica. Home to the world’s largest seed bank, Shearwater was once full of researchers, but with sea levels rising, the Salts are now its final inhabitants. Until, during the worst storm the island has ever seen, a woman mysteriously washes ashore. Isolation has taken its toll on the Salts, but as they nurse the woman, Rowan, back to strength, it begins to feel like she might just be what they need. Rowan, long accustomed to protecting herself, starts imagining a future where she could belong to someone again. But Rowan isn’t telling the whole truth about why she set out for Shearwater. And when she discovers sabotaged radios and a freshly dug grave, she realizes Dominic is keeping his own secrets. As the storms on Shearwater gather force, they all must decide if they can trust each other enough to protect the precious seeds in their care before it’s too late—and if they can finally put the tragedies of the past behind them to create something new, together. A novel of breathtaking twists, dizzying beauty, and ferocious love, Wild Dark Shore is about the impossible choices we make to protect the people we love, even as the world around us disappears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-03-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 312&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781250827999&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=5wcAEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Wild Dark Shore cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=5wcAEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=5wcAEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781250827999</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-03-04T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wedding People by Alison Espach</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Wedding+People&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-08-13&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781420526912&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Wedding People cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Wedding+People&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781420526912</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-08-13T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cribsheet by Emily Oster</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=zGJjDwAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; From the author of Expecting Better, The Family Firm, and The Unexpected an economist&#39;s guide to the early years of parenting. “Both refreshing and useful. With so many parenting theories driving us all a bit batty, this is the type of book that we need to help calm things down.” —LA Times “The book is jampacked with information, but it’s also a delightful read because Oster is such a good writer.” —NPR With Expecting Better, award-winning economist Emily Oster spotted a need in the pregnancy market for advice that gave women the information they needed to make the best decision for their own pregnancies. By digging into the data, Oster found that much of the conventional pregnancy wisdom was wrong. In Cribsheet, she now tackles an even greater challenge: decision-making in the early years of parenting. As any new parent knows, there is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled at you from doctors, family, friends, and strangers on the internet. From the earliest days, parents get the message that they must make certain choices around feeding, sleep, and schedule or all will be lost. There&#39;s a rule—or three—for everything. But the benefits of these choices can be overstated, and the trade-offs can be profound. How do you make your own best decision? Armed with the data, Oster finds that the conventional wisdom doesn&#39;t always hold up. She debunks myths around breastfeeding (not a panacea), sleep training (not so bad!), potty training (wait until they&#39;re ready or possibly bribe with M&amp;Ms), language acquisition (early talkers aren&#39;t necessarily geniuses), and many other topics. She also shows parents how to think through freighted questions like if and how to go back to work, how to think about toddler discipline, and how to have a relationship and parent at the same time. Economics is the science of decision-making, and Cribsheet is a thinking parent&#39;s guide to the chaos and frequent misinformation of the early years. Emily Oster is a trained expert—and mom of two—who can empower us to make better, less fraught decisions—and stay sane in the years before preschool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2019-04-23&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 353&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Family &amp; Relationships&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780525559269&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=zGJjDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Cribsheet cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=zGJjDwAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=zGJjDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780525559269</guid>
      <dc:date>2019-04-23T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problematic Summer Romance by Ali Hazelwood</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Problematic+Summer+Romance%2Binauthor:Ali+Hazelwood&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; What is wrong meets what feels right in this romance set in Italy by the New York Times bestselling author of Deep End. Maya Killgore is twenty-three and still in the process of figuring out her life. Conor Harkness is thirty-eight, and Maya cannot stop thinking about him. It’s such a cliché, it almost makes her heart implode: older man and younger woman; successful biotech guy and struggling grad student; brother’s best friend and the girl he never even knew existed. As Conor loves to remind her, the power dynamic is too imbalanced. Any relationship between them would be problematic in too many ways to count, and Maya should just get over him. After all, he has made it clear that he wants her gone from his life. But not everything is as it seems—and clichés sometimes become plot twists. When Maya’s brother decides to get married in Taormina, she and Conor end up stuck together in a romantic Sicilian villa for over a week. There, on the beautiful Ionian coast, between ancient ruins, delicious foods, and natural caves, Maya realizes that Conor might be hiding something from her. And as the destination wedding begins to erupt out of control, she decides that a summer fling might be just what she needs—even if it’s a problematic one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-05-27&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 417&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9798217187430&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Problematic Summer Romance cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Problematic+Summer+Romance%2Binauthor:Ali+Hazelwood&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798217187430</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-05-27T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom of Claw by Demi Winters</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Kingdom+of+Claw&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Return to the Kingdom of Íseldur, where enemies become lovers and dark secrets hide around each corner, in the sequel to the Viking-inspired romantic fantasy The Road of Bones. In the aftermath of a harrowing journey, Silla Nordvig’s dreams of a simple life have been shattered. Beaten, betrayed, and reeling from the revelation of her true name, she flees Kopa with Reynir Galtung, the ruthless leader of the Bloodaxe Crew. But when they&#39;re forced into hiding together, Silla soon discovers that Rey has been keeping secrets of his own. Stuck in a shield-home with the murderous man she thought she knew, Silla forms a new plan: master the magic flowing through her veins to save her sister. But before she can do that, Silla must face her most formidable opponent yet—her own inner demons. Saga Volsik has nothing to lose. They’ve murdered her family. Stolen her throne. And now they expect her to marry their son, but not if she can dismantle Queen Signe’s plans first. The only problem? The handsome Zagadkian dignitary who knows far too many of her secrets. Silla and Saga will need to find the strength to step into their destiny and stop chaos from sweeping across the land. Meanwhile, dark threads continue to weave themselves through Íseldur as magic long thought dead begins to wake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-02-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 657&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593975633&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Kingdom of Claw cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Kingdom+of+Claw&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593975633</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-02-04T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sounds Like Love by Ashley Poston</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=jPUhEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; A hitmaking songwriter and a bitter musician share a startling and inexplicable connection that they’ll do anything to shake, in the next sparkling, magical book from the New York Times bestselling author of The Seven Year Slip and A Novel Love Story. Named a Most Anticipated book of Summer 2025 by The New York Times ∙ People ∙ USA Today ∙ Marie Claire ∙ E! News ∙ Brit + Co ∙ Yahoo! Life ∙ She Reads ∙ and more! Joni Lark has a secret. She’s one of the most coveted songwriters in LA, and yet she can’t write. There’s an emptiness inside her, and nothing seems to fill it. When she returns to her hometown of Vienna Shores, North Carolina, she hopes that the sand, the surf, and the concerts at The Revelry, her family’s music venue, will spark inspiration. But when Joni gets there, nothing is how she left it. Her best friend is hiding something, her mother’s memories are fading fast, and The Revelry is closing. How can Joni write when her world is leaving her behind? Until she hears it. A melody in her head, lyric-less and half-formed, and an alluring and addictive voice to go with it—belonging, apparently, to a wry musician with an emptiness of his own. Surely, he’s a figment of Joni’s overworked imagination. Then a very real man shows up in Vienna Shores. He’s arrogant and guarded—nothing like the sweet, funny voice in Joni’s head—and he has a plan for breaking their inconvenient telepathic connection: finish the song haunting them both and hope they don’t risk their hearts—or their secrets—in the process. Because that melody, the one drawing them together . . . what if it’s there for a reason?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-06-17&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 385&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593641019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=jPUhEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Sounds Like Love cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=jPUhEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=jPUhEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593641019</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-06-17T00:00:00+09:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2025-08-13T18:22:21+09:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>