<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>MoneyDiariesACTIVE Book Recommendations</title>
    <link>https://reddit.com/r/MoneyDiariesACTIVE</link>
    <description>Monthly book recommendations from r/MoneyDiariesACTIVE</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:11:44 +1000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Atmosphere: A GMA Book Club Pick by Taylor Jenkins Reid</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=RqYtEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Atmosphere%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; GOOD MORNING AMERICA BOOK CLUB PICK • From the #1 New York Times bestselling author of The Seven Husbands of Evelyn Hugo and Daisy Jones &amp; The Six comes an epic new novel set against the backdrop of the 1980s space shuttle program about the extraordinary lengths we go to live and love beyond our limits. The stunning hardcover of Atmosphere features beautiful endpapers and a premium dust jacket! “Thrilling . . . heartbreaking . . . uplifting . . . the fast-paced, emotionally charged story of one ambitious young woman, finding both her voice and her passion.”—Kristin Hannah, author of The Women “NASA? Space missions? The ’80s? This is a collection of all the things I love.”—Andy Weir, author of Project Hail Mary and The Martian Joan Goodwin has been obsessed with the stars for as long as she can remember. Thoughtful and reserved, Joan is content with her life as a professor of physics and astronomy at Rice University and as aunt to her precocious niece, Frances. That is, until she comes across an advertisement seeking the first women scientists to join NASA’s space shuttle program. Suddenly, Joan burns to be one of the few people to go to space. Selected from a pool of thousands of applicants in the summer of 1980, Joan begins training at Houston’s Johnson Space Center, alongside an exceptional group of fellow candidates: Top Gun pilot Hank Redmond and scientist John Griffin, who are kind and easygoing even when the stakes are highest; mission specialist Lydia Danes, who has worked too hard to play nice; warmhearted Donna Fitzgerald, who is navigating her own secrets; and Vanessa Ford, the magnetic and mysterious aeronautical engineer, who can fix any engine and fly any plane. As the new astronauts become unlikely friends and prepare for their first flights, Joan finds a passion and a love she never imagined. In this new light, Joan begins to question everything she thinks she knows about her place in the observable universe. Then, in December of 1984, on mission STS-LR9, it all changes in an instant. Fast-paced, thrilling, and emotional, Atmosphere is Taylor Jenkins Reid at her best: transporting readers to iconic times and places, creating complex protagonists, and telling a passionate and soaring story about the transformative power of love—this time among the stars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-06-03&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 353&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593158715&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=RqYtEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Atmosphere: A GMA Book Club Pick cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=RqYtEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Atmosphere%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=RqYtEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593158715</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-06-03T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&quot;A Secret to be Burried&quot; by Emily Hawley Gillespie</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=dR96AAAAMAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; The sound of nineteenth-century women, once thought lost to us, is alive because ordinary women like Emily Hawley Gillespie gave voice to their thoughts in diaries. This condensed version of the 2,500-page journals of Emily Gillespie, faithfully written from 1858 to 1888, is a detailed account of rural Iowa life. More than this, it contains the reflections of a woman who dreamed of being a painter and writer and instead became a wife and a mother, a woman whose radical convictions were recorded in her diary, while publicly she conformed to the prescribed life of a Victorian pioneer woman. Through Emily&#39;s journals, readers are offered immediate and unmodified contact with settlers in Iowa one hundred years ago. A wealth of facts are includedOCowhat produce she harvested and preserved from her garden, how her husband tended his fields and what he raised, the challenges and rewards of family life. Judy Lensink&#39;s skillful analysis shows the larger patterns in Emily Gillespie&#39;s life and provides keys that unlock the diary&#39;s secrets. Emily&#39;s life is revealed as a youth full of promise fading into middle and declining years of lost dreams and eventual tragedy, which caused her to write, I have written &quot;many&quot; things in my journal, but the worst is a secret to be burried when I shall cease to be.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 1989&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 480&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Biography &amp; Autobiography&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=dR96AAAAMAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;A Secret to be Burried&quot; cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=dR96AAAAMAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=dR96AAAAMAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 1989 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">&quot;a-secret-to-be-burried&quot;-emily-hawley-gillespie</guid>
      <dc:date>1989-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Sisters by Coco Mellors</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Blue+Sisters%2Binauthor:Coco+Mellors&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; From the Sunday Times bestselling author of Cleopatra and Frankenstein ﻿&#39;A stunning exploration of sisterhood and grief, addiction and recovery, pain and pleasure. Captivating&#39; TESS GUNTY &#39;In Blue Sisters, grief is rendered with gorgeous particularity&#39; RAVEN LEILANI&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-05-21&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 384&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780008623012&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Blue Sisters cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Blue+Sisters%2Binauthor:Coco+Mellors&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=B9atEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780008623012</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-05-21T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The God of the Woods by Liz Moore</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=krLfEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+God+of+the+Woods&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; AN INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER AN AMAZON BEST BOOK OF 2024 WINNER OF GOODREADS MYSTERY &amp; THRILLER BOOK OF THE YEAR 2024 &#39;I was totally gripped&#39; DOUGLAS STUART &#39;Immersive and enthralling&#39; PAULA HAWKINS &#39;At first hard to put down. By page 200, impossible&#39; STEPHEN KING ––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––––&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-07-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 524&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780008663810&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=krLfEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The God of the Woods cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=krLfEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+God+of+the+Woods&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=krLfEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780008663810</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-07-04T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild Dark Shore by Charlotte McConaghy</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=5WI8EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Wild+Dark+Shore&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; &#39;At once a gripping mystery, an exquisitely written ode to the natural world, and a taut, psychological thriller, Wild Dark Shore is a triumph. Charlotte McConaghy is masterful in her ability to show the intricate connections between place and the human heart, and Wild Dark Shore shows her at the height of her powers. Breathtaking.&#39; HANNAH KENT Dominic Salt and his three children are caretakers of Shearwater, a tiny island not far from Antarctica. Home to the world&#39;s largest seed bank, Shearwater was once full of researchers. But with sea levels rising, the Salts are now its final inhabitants, packing up the seeds before they are transported to safer ground. Despite the wild beauty of life here, isolation has taken its toll on the Salts. Raff, 18 and suffering his first heartbreak, can only find relief at his punching bag; Fen, 17, has started spending her nights on the beach among the seals; 9-year-old Orly, obsessed with botany, fears the loss of his beloved natural world; and Dominic can&#39;t stop turning back towards the past, and the loss that drove the family to Shearwater in the first place. Then, during the worst storm the island has ever seen, a woman washes up on shore. As the Salts nurse the woman, Rowan, back to life, their suspicion gives way to affection, and they finally begin to feel like a family again. Rowan, long accustomed to protecting her heart, begins to fall for the Salts, too. But Rowan isn&#39;t telling the whole truth about why she set out for Shearwater. And when she discovers the sabotaged radios and a freshly dug grave, she realises Dominic is keeping his own dark secrets. As the storms on Shearwater gather force, the characters must decide if they can trust each other enough to protect the precious seeds in their care before it&#39;s too late-and if they can finally put the tragedies of the past behind them to create something new, together. A novel of heartstopping twists, dizzying beauty and ferocious love, Wild Dark Shore is a story about the impossible choices we make to protect the people we love, even as the world around us is ending.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-03-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 322&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781761620003&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=5WI8EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Wild Dark Shore cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=5WI8EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Wild+Dark+Shore&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=5WI8EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781761620003</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-03-04T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wedding People by Alison Espach</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Wedding+People&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-08-13&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781420526912&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Wedding People cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Wedding+People&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Wvw_0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781420526912</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-08-13T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cribsheet by Emily Oster</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=epaYDwAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Cribsheet%2Binauthor:Emily+Oster&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; &#39;Emily Oster is the non-judgemental girlfriend holding our hand and guiding us through pregnancy and motherhood. She has done the work to get us the hard facts in a soft, understandable way&#39; Amy Schumer Parenting is full of decisions, nearly all of which can be agonized over. There is an abundance of often-conflicting advice hurled at you from doctors, family, friends, and strangers on the internet. But the benefits of these choices can be overstated, and the trade-offs can be profound. How do you make your own best decision? Armed with the data, Oster finds that the conventional wisdom doesn&#39;t always hold up. She debunks myths and offers non-judgemental ways to consider our options in light of the facts. Cribsheet is a thinking parent&#39;s guide that empowers us to make better, less fraught decisions - and stay sane in the years before preschool. *Now you can navigate the primary school years with Emily Oster too, in her new book The Family Firm, out now*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2019-05-30&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 390&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Family &amp; Relationships&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781782836551&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=epaYDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Cribsheet cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=epaYDwAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Cribsheet%2Binauthor:Emily+Oster&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=epaYDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781782836551</guid>
      <dc:date>2019-05-30T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problematic Summer Romance by Ali Hazelwood</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Problematic+Summer+Romance%2Binauthor:Ali+Hazelwood&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; What is wrong meets what feels right in this romance set in Italy by the New York Times bestselling author of Deep End. Maya Killgore is twenty-three and still in the process of figuring out her life. Conor Harkness is thirty-eight, and Maya cannot stop thinking about him. It’s such a cliché, it almost makes her heart implode: older man and younger woman; successful biotech guy and struggling grad student; brother’s best friend and the girl he never even knew existed. As Conor loves to remind her, the power dynamic is too imbalanced. Any relationship between them would be problematic in too many ways to count, and Maya should just get over him. After all, he has made it clear that he wants her gone from his life. But not everything is as it seems—and clichés sometimes become plot twists. When Maya’s brother decides to get married in Taormina, she and Conor end up stuck together in a romantic Sicilian villa for over a week. There, on the beautiful Ionian coast, between ancient ruins, delicious foods, and natural caves, Maya realizes that Conor might be hiding something from her. And as the destination wedding begins to erupt out of control, she decides that a summer fling might be just what she needs—even if it’s a problematic one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-05-27&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 417&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9798217187430&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Problematic Summer Romance cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Problematic+Summer+Romance%2Binauthor:Ali+Hazelwood&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=OslYEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798217187430</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-05-27T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom of Claw by Demi Winters</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Kingdom+of+Claw&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Return to the Kingdom of Íseldur, where enemies become lovers and dark secrets hide around each corner, in the sequel to the Viking-inspired romantic fantasy The Road of Bones. In the aftermath of a harrowing journey, Silla Nordvig’s dreams of a simple life have been shattered. Beaten, betrayed, and reeling from the revelation of her true name, she flees Kopa with Reynir Galtung, the ruthless leader of the Bloodaxe Crew. But when they&#39;re forced into hiding together, Silla soon discovers that Rey has been keeping secrets of his own. Stuck in a shield-home with the murderous man she thought she knew, Silla forms a new plan: master the magic flowing through her veins to save her sister. But before she can do that, Silla must face her most formidable opponent yet—her own inner demons. Saga Volsik has nothing to lose. They’ve murdered her family. Stolen her throne. And now they expect her to marry their son, but not if she can dismantle Queen Signe’s plans first. The only problem? The handsome Zagadkian dignitary who knows far too many of her secrets. Silla and Saga will need to find the strength to step into their destiny and stop chaos from sweeping across the land. Meanwhile, dark threads continue to weave themselves through Íseldur as magic long thought dead begins to wake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-02-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 657&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593975633&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Kingdom of Claw cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Kingdom+of+Claw&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lZ4GEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593975633</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-02-04T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sounds Like Love by Ashley Poston</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=K_shEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Sounds+like+Love%2Binauthor:Ashley+Poston&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; A hitmaking songwriter and a bitter musician share a startling and inexplicable connection that they’ll do anything to shake, in the next sparkling, magical book from the New York Times bestselling author of The Seven Year Slip and A Novel Love Story. Named a Most Anticipated book of Summer 2025 by People ∙ Marie Claire ∙ Brit + Co ∙ Yahoo! Life ∙ She Reads ∙ and more! Joni Lark has a secret. She’s one of the most coveted songwriters in LA, and yet she can’t write. There’s an emptiness inside her, and nothing seems to fill it. When she returns to her hometown of Vienna Shores, North Carolina, she hopes that the sand, the surf, and the concerts at The Revelry, her family’s music venue, will spark inspiration. But when Joni gets there, nothing is how she left it. Her best friend is hiding something, her mother’s memories are fading fast, and The Revelry is closing. How can Joni write when her world is leaving her behind? Until she hears it. A melody in her head, lyric-less and half-formed, and an alluring and addictive voice to go with it—belonging, apparently, to a wry musician with an emptiness of his own. Surely, he’s a figment of Joni’s overworked imagination. Then a very real man shows up in Vienna Shores. He’s arrogant and guarded—nothing like the sweet, funny voice in Joni’s head—and he has a plan for breaking their inconvenient telepathic connection: finish the song haunting them both and hope they don’t risk their hearts—or their secrets—in the process. Because that melody, the one drawing them together . . . what if it’s there for a reason?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-06-17&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 385&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593641026&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=K_shEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Sounds Like Love cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=K_shEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Sounds+like+Love%2Binauthor:Ashley+Poston&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=K_shEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593641026</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-06-17T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermezzo by Sally Rooney</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=ifn3EAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Intermezzo%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; THE INSTANT #1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER • Shortlisted for the British Book Awards 2025 • Shortlisted for the An Post Irish Book Awards Novel of the Year • Best Book of the Year: The New Yorker • The New York Times • The Globe and Mail • TIME • The Winnipeg Free Press • The Guardian • The Independent • NPR • Dazed • VOX • People • Kirkus Reviews • Publishers Weekly • An exquisitely moving story about grief, love and family, from the global phenomenon Sally Rooney. Aside from the fact that they are brothers, Peter and Ivan Koubek seem to have little in common. Peter is a Dublin lawyer in his thirties – successful, competent and apparently unassailable. But in the wake of their father’s death, he’s medicating himself to sleep and struggling to manage his relationships with two very different women – his enduring first love, Sylvia, and Naomi, a college student for whom life is one long joke. Ivan is a twenty-two-year-old competitive chess player. He has always seen himself as socially awkward, a loner, the antithesis of his glib elder brother. Now, in the early weeks of his bereavement, Ivan meets Margaret, an older woman emerging from her own turbulent past, and their lives become rapidly and intensely intertwined. For two grieving brothers and the people they love, this is a new interlude – a period of desire, despair and possibility – a chance to find out how much one life might hold inside itself without breaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-09-24&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 449&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780735281820&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ifn3EAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Intermezzo cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=ifn3EAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Intermezzo%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ifn3EAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780735281820</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-09-24T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beautiful World, Where Are You by Sally Rooney</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=VJETEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Beautiful+World,+Where+Are+You%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; ** Pre-order Sally Rooney&#39;s new novel Intermezzo now ** THE SUNDAY TIMES AND GLOBAL NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER WINNER OF NOVEL OF THE YEAR AT THE AN POST IRISH BOOK AWARDS OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD ACROSS ALL FABER EDITIONS &#39;A tour de force.&#39; Anne Enright, Guardian &#39;Rooney&#39;s best novel yet.&#39; Brandon Taylor, New York Times &#39;Get ready to have your heart broken all over again.&#39; Red &#39;The book moved me to tears more than once.&#39; The Times Alice, a novelist, meets Felix, who works in a warehouse, and asks him if he&#39;d like to travel to Rome with her. In Dublin, her best friend Eileen is getting over a break-up and slips back into flirting with Simon, a man she has known since childhood. Alice, Felix, Eileen and Simon are still young - but life is catching up with them. They desire each other, they delude each other, they worry about sex and friendship and the times they live in. Will they find a way to believe in a beautiful world? Sally Rooney&#39;s book Beautiful World, Where Are You was a #1 Sunday Times bestseller w/c 11-09-2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2021-09-07&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 323&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780571365456&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=VJETEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Beautiful World, Where Are You cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=VJETEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Beautiful+World,+Where+Are+You%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=VJETEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780571365456</guid>
      <dc:date>2021-09-07T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversations with Friends by Sally Rooney</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=WbtvDgAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Conversations+with+Friends%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; ** Pre-order Sally Rooney&#39;s new novel Intermezzo now ** &#39;A nuanced, page-turning portrait.&#39; Zadie Smith &#39;Brilliant.&#39; Marian Keyes &#39;A sharp, darkly funny comment on modern relationships.&#39; Sunday Telegraph The critically-acclaimed debut novel from the globally bestselling author of Normal People and Beautiful World, Where Are You. Frances is twenty-one years old, cool-headed and observant. At night she performs spoken word with her best friend Bobbi, who used to be her girlfriend. When they are befriended by Melissa, a well-known journalist who is married to Nick, an actor, they enter a world of beautiful houses, raucous dinner parties and holidays in Provence, beginning a complex ménage-à-quatre. But when Frances and Nick get unexpectedly closer, Frances is forced to honestly confront her own vulnerabilities for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2017-05-25&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 305&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780571333141&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=WbtvDgAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Conversations with Friends cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=WbtvDgAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Conversations+with+Friends%2Binauthor:Sally+Rooney&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=WbtvDgAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780571333141</guid>
      <dc:date>2017-05-25T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grape Juice by Eliza Dumais</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=p7Ic0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Grape+Juice%2Binauthor:Eliza+Dumais&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; For fans of Under the Tuscan Sun, French Kiss, and The Pairing. In her life in NYC, Alice feels like she&#39;s withering on the vine. So when her boss suggests she attend wine harvest in rural France, she&#39;s on a plane faster than she can second-guess herself. On her first day of alcohol-addled adult summer camp, she&#39;s paired with Henri--equally disillusioned, albeit in his own very French way--and she realizes just how much can change if she&#39;s willing to get her hands dirty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-11-04&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9798893310566&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=p7Ic0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Grape Juice cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=p7Ic0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Grape+Juice%2Binauthor:Eliza+Dumais&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=p7Ic0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798893310566</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-11-04T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle of the Bookstores by Ali Brady</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=MegeEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Battle+of+the+Bookstores%2Binauthor:Ali+Brady&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Rivalry and romance spark when two bookstore managers who are opposites in every way find themselves competing for the same promotion. Despite managing bookstores on the same Boston street, Josie Klein and Ryan Lawson have never interacted much—Josie’s store focuses on serious literature, and Ryan’s sells romance only. But when the new owner of both stores decides to combine them, the two are thrust into direct competition. Only one manager will be left standing, decided by who turns the most profit over the summer. Efficient and detail-oriented Josie instantly clashes with easygoing and disorganized Ryan. Their competing events and contrasting styles lead to more than just frustration—the sparks between them might just set the whole store on fire. Their only solace during this chaos is the friendship they’ve each struck up with an anonymous friend in an online book forum. Little do they know they’re actually chatting with each other. As their rivalry heats up in real life, their online relationship grows, and when the walls between their stores come tumbling down, Josie and Ryan realize not all’s fair in love and war. And maybe, if they’re lucky, happily ever afters aren’t just for the books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-06-03&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 433&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593640845&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=MegeEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Battle of the Bookstores cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=MegeEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Battle+of+the+Bookstores%2Binauthor:Ali+Brady&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=MegeEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593640845</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-06-03T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>None of This Is True by Lisa Jewell</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=IS43EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:None+of+This+is+True&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Over 1 million copies sold! This unputdownable psychological thriller by New York Times bestselling author Lisa Jewell follows a woman who finds herself the subject of her own popular true crime podcast. Celebrating her forty-fifth birthday at her local pub, popular podcaster Alix Summer crosses paths with an unassuming woman called Josie Fair. Josie, it turns out, is also celebrating her forty-fifth birthday. They are, in fact, birthday twins. A few days later, Alix and Josie bump into each other again, this time outside Alix’s children’s school. Josie has been listening to Alix’s podcasts and thinks she might be an interesting subject for her series. She is, she tells Alix, on the cusp of great changes in her life. Josie’s life appears to be strange and complicated, and although Alix finds her unsettling, she can’t quite resist the temptation to keep making the podcast. Slowly she starts to realize that Josie has been hiding some very dark secrets, and before she knows it, Josie has inveigled her way into Alix’s life—and into her home. But, as quickly as she arrived, Josie disappears. Only then does Alix discover that Josie has left a terrible and terrifying legacy in her wake, and that Alix has become the subject of her own true crime podcast, with her life and her family’s lives under mortal threat. Who is Josie Fair? And what has she done?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-01-07&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 400&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781982179014&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=IS43EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;None of This Is True cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=IS43EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:None+of+This+is+True&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=IS43EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781982179014</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-01-07T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remarkably Bright Creatures by Shelby Van Pelt</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=jo9AEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Remarkably+Bright+Creatures&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Have you met Marcellus the octopus yet? **THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** OVER HALF A MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE BBC RADIO 2 BOOK CLUB PICK OVER 29,000 5 STAR REVIEWS GOOD HOUSEKEEPING BEST BOOKS OF 2022 GLAMOUR BEST BOOKS OF 2022 &#39;Full of heart and humour . . . I loved it.&#39; Ruth Hogan &#39;Will stay with you for a long time.&#39; Anstey Harris &#39;I defy you to put it down once you&#39;ve started&#39; Cynthia D&#39;Aprix Sweeney After Tova Sullivan&#39;s husband died, she began working the night cleaner shift at the Sowell Bay Aquarium. Ever since her eighteen-year-old son, Erik, mysteriously vanished on a boat over thirty years ago keeping busy has helped her cope. One night she meets Marcellus, a giant Pacific octopus living at the aquarium who sees everything, but wouldn&#39;t dream of lifting one of his eight arms for his human captors – until he forms a remarkable friendship with Tova. Ever the detective, Marcellus deduces what happened the night Tova&#39;s son disappeared. And now Marcellus must use every trick his old body can muster to unearth the truth for her before it&#39;s too late... Shelby Van Pelt&#39;s debut novel is a reminder that sometimes taking a hard look at the past can help uncover a future that once felt impossible. &#39;You won&#39;t be able to put it down because when you&#39;re not reading this book you&#39;ll be hugging it.&#39; Jamie Ford &#39;Truly original and touching&#39; Helen Hoang &#39;Unique and luminous&#39; Booklist starred review __________________________ READER REVIEWS &#39;I couldn&#39;t put it down&#39; &#39;Marvelous, heartwarming, brilliant&#39; &#39;I enjoyed every second&#39; &#39;I was gripped from the first page&#39; &#39;I was completely charmed by this story&#39;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2022-05-26&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 385&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781526649683&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=jo9AEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Remarkably Bright Creatures cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=jo9AEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Remarkably+Bright+Creatures&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=jo9AEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781526649683</guid>
      <dc:date>2022-05-26T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ghost Writer by John Harwood</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=6o0rAAAAYAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Ghostwriter&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Plagued with unpleasant memories of his mother&#39;s death, shy Gerard Freeman is obsessed with the manuscript of a century-old ghost story written by his great-grandmother and entrusted to his care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2004&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 392&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=6o0rAAAAYAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Ghost Writer cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=6o0rAAAAYAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Ghostwriter&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=6o0rAAAAYAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">the-ghost-writer-john-harwood</guid>
      <dc:date>2004-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Lie Wins by Ashley Elston</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=do26zwEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:First+Lie+Wins&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Evie Porter has everything a nice, Southern girl could want: a perfect, doting boyfriend, a house with a white picket fence and a garden, a fancy group of friends. The only catch: Evie Porter doesn&#39;t exist. The identity comes first: Evie Porter. Once she&#39;s given a name and location by her mysterious boss Mr. Smith, she learns everything there is to know about the town and the people in it. Then the mark: Ryan Sumner. The last piece of the puzzle is the job. Evie isn&#39;t privy to Mr. Smith&#39;s real identity, but she knows this job will be different. Ryan has gotten under her skin, and she&#39;s starting to envision a different sort of life for herself. But Evie can&#39;t make any mistakes--especially after what happened last time. Because the one thing she&#39;s worked her entire life to keep clean, the one identity she could always go back to-her real identity-just walked right into this town. Evie Porter must stay one step ahead of her past while making sure there&#39;s still a future in front of her. The stakes couldn&#39;t be higher--but then, Evie has always liked a challenge...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-01-02&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781472295323&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=do26zwEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;First Lie Wins cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=do26zwEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:First+Lie+Wins&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=do26zwEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781472295323</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-01-02T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow Horses by Mick Herron</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=taAEAQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; THE BOOK BEHIND THE FIRST SEASON OF SLOW HORSES, THE APPLE ORIGINAL SERIES STARRING GARY OLDMAN IN HIS EMMY-NOMINATED ROLE AS JACKSON LAMB. Welcome to the thrilling and unnervingly prescient world of the slow horses. This team of MI5 agents is united by one common bond: They&#39;ve screwed up royally and will do anything to redeem themselves. This deluxe edition of a modern classic includes a foreword by the author, discussion questions for book clubs, and an exclusive short story featuring the slow horses. London, England: Slough House is where washed-up MI5 spies go to while away what’s left of their failed careers. The “slow horses,” as they’re called, have all disgraced themselves in some way to get relegated there. Maybe they botched an Op so badly they can’t be trusted anymore. Maybe they got in the way of an ambitious colleague and had the rug yanked out from under them. Maybe they just got too dependent on the bottle—not unusual in this line of work. One thing they have in common, though, is they want to be back in the action. And most of them would do anything to get there─even if it means having to collaborate with one another. When a young man is abducted and his kidnappers threaten to broadcast his beheading live on the Internet, the slow horses see an opportunity to redeem themselves. But is the victim really who he appears to be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2010-06-01&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 258&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781569479018&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=taAEAQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Slow Horses cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=taAEAQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=taAEAQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781569479018</guid>
      <dc:date>2010-06-01T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silverborn by Jessica Townsend</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=ZlHpzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Silverborn%2Binauthor:Jessica+Townsend&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-09-26&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Juvenile Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781510107373&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ZlHpzgEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Silverborn cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=ZlHpzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Silverborn%2Binauthor:Jessica+Townsend&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ZlHpzgEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781510107373</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-09-26T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Buffalo Hunter Hunter by Stephen Graham Jones</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=Mx4OEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; An instant New York Times bestseller, a chilling historical horror novel tracing the life of a vampire who haunts the fields of the Blackfeet reservation looking for justice. A diary, written in 1912 by a Lutheran pastor is discovered within a wall. What it unveils is a slow massacre, a chain of events that go back to 217 Blackfeet dead in the snow. Told in transcribed interviews by a Blackfeet named Good Stab, who shares the narrative of his peculiar life over a series of confessional visits. This is an American Indian revenge story written by one of the new masters of horror, Stephen Graham Jones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-03-18&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 448&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781668075104&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Mx4OEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Buffalo Hunter Hunter cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=Mx4OEQAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Mx4OEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781668075104</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-03-18T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broken Country by Clare Leslie Hall</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=4VtMEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Broken+Country&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; “Stirring and mysterious…fires directly at the human heart and hits the mark.” —Delia Owens, New York Times bestselling author of Where the Crawdads Sing A love triangle unearths dangerous, deadly secrets from the past in this thrilling tale perfect for fans of The Paper Palace and Where the Crawdads Sing. “The farmer is dead. He is dead, and all anyone wants to know is who killed him.” Beth and her gentle, kind husband Frank are happily married, but their relationship relies on the past staying buried. But when Beth’s brother-in-law shoots a dog going after their sheep, Beth doesn’t realize that the gunshot will alter the course of their lives. For the dog belonged to none other than Gabriel Wolfe, the man Beth loved as a teenager—the man who broke her heart years ago. Gabriel has returned to the village with his young son Leo, a boy who reminds Beth very much of her own son, who died in a tragic accident. As Beth is pulled back into Gabriel’s life, tensions around the village rise and dangerous secrets and jealousies from the past resurface, this time with deadly consequences. Beth is forced to make a choice between the woman she once was, and the woman she has become. A sweeping love story with the pace and twists of a thriller, Broken Country is a novel of simmering passion, impossible choices, and explosive consequences that toggles between the past and present to explore the far-reaching legacy of first love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-03-04&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 320&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781668078181&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=4VtMEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Broken Country cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=4VtMEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Broken+Country&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=4VtMEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781668078181</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-03-04T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Compound by Aisling Rawle</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=bYM1EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Compound%2Binauthor:Aisling+Rawle&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; ‘Lord of the Flies meets Love Island – dark, thrilling, and delightfully twisted’ LOUISE O&#39;NEILL &#39;So gripping and propulsive that it beats reality TV at its own game. Why watch TV when Aisling Rawle does it better?&#39; TORREY PETERS &#39;THIS is the book to read this summer. Easily one of my favourite novels I’ve read this year... 10 out of 10&#39; CECELIA AHERN&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-07-03&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 351&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780008710101&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=bYM1EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Compound cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=bYM1EQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Compound%2Binauthor:Aisling+Rawle&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=bYM1EQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780008710101</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-07-03T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Julie Chan Is Dead by Liann Zhang</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=7R9TEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Julie+Chan+is+Dead%2Binauthor:Liann+Zhang&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; In this debut thriller perfect for fans of Bunny and Yellowface, a young woman steps into her deceased twin’s influencer life, only to discover dark secrets hidden behind her social media façade. Julie Chan has nothing. Her twin sister has everything. Except a pulse. Julie Chan, a supermarket cashier with nothing to lose, finds herself thrust into the glamorous yet perilous world of her late twin sister, Chloe VanHuusen, a popular influencer. Separated at a young age, the identical twins were polar opposites and rarely spoke, except for one viral video that Chloe initiated (Finding My Long-Lost Twin And Buying Her A House #EMOTIONAL). When Julie discovers Chloe’s lifeless body under mysterious circumstances, she seizes the chance to live the life she’s always envied. Transforming into Chloe is easier than expected. Julie effortlessly adopts Chloe’s luxurious influencer life, complete with designer clothes, a meticulous skincare routine, and millions of adoring followers. However, Julie soon realizes that Chloe’s seemingly picture-perfect life was anything but. Haunted by Chloe’s untimely death and struggling to fit into the privileged influencer circle, Julie faces mounting challenges during a weeklong island retreat with Chloe’s exclusive group of influencer friends. As events spiral out of control, Julie uncovers the sinister forces that may have led to her sister’s demise and realizes she might be the next target.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-04-29&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 320&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781668067895&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7R9TEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Julie Chan Is Dead cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=7R9TEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Julie+Chan+is+Dead%2Binauthor:Liann+Zhang&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7R9TEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781668067895</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-04-29T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care and Feeding by Laurie Woolever</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=mBwi0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Care+and+Feeding%2Binauthor:Laurie+Woolever&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Laurie Woolever - co-author of bestsellers Appetites and Bourdain: The Definitive Oral Biography - traces her path from a small-town childhood to working at food publications and revered restaurants in New York and around the world with two of the most powerful men in the business: Mario Batali and Anthony Bourdain. But there&#39;s more to this story than the two bold-faced names on her resume. Behind the scenes, Laurie&#39;s life is chaotic, an often-pleasurable buffet of bad decisions at which she frequently overstays her welcome. Acerbic and wryly self-deprecating, Laurie attempts to carve out her own space as a woman in a world both toxic and intoxicating, while balancing her consuming work with a sometimes-ambivalent relationship to marriage and motherhood. As the food world careens towards an overdue reckoning and Laurie&#39;s mentors face their own high-profile descents, she is confronted with the questions of where she belongs and how to hold on to the parts of her life&#39;s work that she truly values: care and feeding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-03-25&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Biography &amp; Autobiography&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781923293267&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=mBwi0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Care and Feeding cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=mBwi0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Care+and+Feeding%2Binauthor:Laurie+Woolever&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=mBwi0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781923293267</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honey by Isabel Banta</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=3QXuEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Honey%2Binauthor:Isabel+Banta&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; For fans of Daisy Jones and the Six by Taylor Jenkins Reid, Emma Cline&#39;s The Girls, and Stephanie Danler&#39;s Sweetbitter, a coming-of-age story that follows the stunningly talented popstar Amber Young as she skyrockets to fame in the late 90s.It is 1997 and Amber Young is about to become one of the most infamous pop stars of her era. Plucked from a small town in New Jersey to join the newly formed girl group Cloud9 in Los Angeles, Amber is given the opportunity of a lifetime.Enter Gwen Morris and Wes Kingston, two of Amber&#39;s musical contemporaries who are in a highly publicized relationship. Gwen has the top music video on MTV&#39;s Total Request Live and Wes is a member of the most popular boy band in the world, ETA. In Gwen, Amber finds the first friend who can truly understand her - maybe the only person who ever will. But when Amber goes on tour with ETA as one of their opening acts, she develops an infatuation with Wes that threatens both her friendship with Gwen and the career she is so desperately trying to build. Under the spotlight, Amber is forced to reckon with her own desires, agency, and sense of self - and how the kaleidoscope of public opinion can distort everything.Through meticulous research about this era of pop music, and featuring iconic moments from early 2000s pop culture, Isabel Banta&#39;s debut novel, Honey, reimagines the pop stars of the late 90s and early 2000s, who we idolized and hated, oversexualized and underestimated, giving them the fresh, multifaceted story they deserve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-06-25&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781250333469&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=3QXuEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Honey cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=3QXuEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Honey%2Binauthor:Isabel+Banta&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=3QXuEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781250333469</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-06-25T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Forbidden Alchemy by Stacey McEwan</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=fPFiEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Forbidden+Alchemy%2Binauthor:Stacey+McEwan&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This stunning slow-burn romantasy follows a fated pair who uncover a world-changing secret and are thrust into a violent class war, navigating love, loss, and devastating betrayals. Nina Harrow and Patrick Colson are twelve years old when they are whisked away from the shadows of their disenfranchised mining towns to dazzling Belavere City to discover their magical potential. Those who pass Belavere’s test will become Artisans, wielders of powerful elemental magic destined to fulfill the city’s grand ambitions. For Nina, the Artisan School symbolizes a dream and an escape from her harsh reality, while Patrick yearns to return to his Craftsman family, whose extraordinary physical strength serves the idium mines keeping the city alive. And then they uncover a devastating truth: Artisans aren’t born, they’re chosen. They part ways on very different paths, leaving them to carry the burden of this secret alone. In the years that follow, a Craftsman revolution ignites, thrusting Nina and Patrick into opposing factions of a brewing war. Now an elite Artisan with the very rare talent for charming earth, Nina has turned her back on the fight, haunted by the loss of her found family. But fate intervenes when she is captured by Patrick’s rebel group. Despite the years and conflict that separates them, Patrick hasn’t forgotten Nina. He desperately seeks her help for a mission that could shift the tides against Belavere City. Reluctantly, she agrees, battling the sparks flying between them. But when Nina’s first love reappears, asking her to betray Patrick for the sake of the Artisans, Nina faces an impossible choice that could alter the fate of their world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-07&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 480&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781668076187&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=fPFiEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;A Forbidden Alchemy cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=fPFiEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:A+Forbidden+Alchemy%2Binauthor:Stacey+McEwan&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=fPFiEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781668076187</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-07-01T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Geographer&#39;s Map to Romance by India Holton</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=7xQTEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Geographer%27s+Map+to+Romance%2Binauthor:India+Holton&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Geography professors in a failed marriage of convenience inconveniently reconnect for an emergency mission in this swoony historical-fantasy rom-com. Professor Elodie Tarrant is an expert in magic disasters. Nothing fazes her—except her own personal disaster, that is: Professor Gabriel Tarrant, the grumpy, unfriendly man she married for convenience a year ago, whom she secretly loves. Gabriel is also an expert in magic disasters. And nothing fazes him either—except the walking, talking tornado that is his wife. They’ve been estranged since shortly after their wedding day, but that hasn’t stopped him from stoically pining for her. When magic erupts in a small Welsh village, threatening catastrophe for the rest of Britain, Elodie and Gabriel are accidentally both assigned to the case. With the fate of the country in their hands, they must come together as a team in the face of perilous conditions like explosions, domesticated goats, and only one bed. But this is easier said than done. After all, there&#39;s no navigational guide for the geography of the heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-04-08&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 369&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593641477&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7xQTEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Geographer&#39;s Map to Romance cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=7xQTEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Geographer%27s+Map+to+Romance%2Binauthor:India+Holton&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7xQTEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593641477</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-04-08T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Big Beautiful Life: Reese&#39;s Book Club by Emily Henry</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=Ur8fEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; A REESE’S BOOK CLUB PICK ∙ AN INSTANT #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER ∙ Two writers compete for the chance to tell the larger-than-life story of a woman with more than a couple of plot twists up her sleeve in this dazzling and sweeping novel from Emily Henry. As featured in The New York Times ∙ Rolling Stone ∙ People ∙ Good Morning America ∙ NPR ∙ Vogue ∙ The Cut ∙ USA Today ∙ Cosmopolitan ∙ Harper&#39;s Bazaar ∙ Marie Claire ∙ Glamour ∙ ELLE ∙ E! Online ∙ The New York Post ∙ Bustle ∙ Reader&#39;s Digest ∙ BBC ∙ PopSugar ∙ SheReads ∙ Paste ∙ and more! Alice Scott is an eternal optimist still dreaming of her big writing break. Hayden Anderson is a Pulitzer-prize winning human thundercloud. And they’re both on balmy Little Crescent Island for the same reason: to write the biography of a woman no one has seen in years—or at least to meet with the octogenarian who claims to be the Margaret Ives. Tragic heiress, former tabloid princess, and daughter of one of the most storied (and scandalous) families of the twentieth century. When Margaret invites them both for a one-month trial period, after which she’ll choose the person who’ll tell her story, there are three things keeping Alice’s head in the game. One: Alice genuinely likes people, which means people usually like Alice—and she has a whole month to win the legendary woman over. Two: She’s ready for this job and the chance to impress her perennially unimpressed family with a Serious Publication. Three: Hayden Anderson, who should have no reason to be concerned about losing this book, is glowering at her in a shaken-to-the core way that suggests he sees her as competition. But the problem is, Margaret is only giving each of them pieces of her story. Pieces they can’t swap to put together because of an ironclad NDA and an inconvenient yearning pulsing between them every time they’re in the same room. And it’s becoming abundantly clear that their story—just like the tale Margaret’s spinning—could be a mystery, tragedy, or love ballad . . . depending on who’s telling it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-04-22&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 433&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780593441299&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Ur8fEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Great Big Beautiful Life: Reese&#39;s Book Club cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=Ur8fEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Great+Big+Beautiful+Life%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=Ur8fEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780593441299</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-04-22T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patron Saint of Liars by Ann Patchett</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=hFIeNvnZO4wC&amp;dq=intitle:The+Patron+Saint+of+Liars%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; &quot;Beautifully written...Ann Patchett has produced a first novel that second- and third-time novelists would envy for its grace, insight, and compassion.&quot; BOSTON HERALD St. Elizabeth&#39;s is a home for unwed mothers in the 1960s. Life there is not unpleasant and for most, it is temporary. Not so for Rose, a beautiful mysterious woman who comes to the lovely ex-hotel pregnant, but not unwed. She plans to give her baby up because she knows she cannot be the mother it needs. But St. Elizabeth&#39;s is near a healing spring, and when Rose&#39;s time draws near, she cannot go through with her plans, not all of them. And she cannot remain forever untouched by what she has left behind and who she has become in the leaving....&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 1993-04-24&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 324&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780804111515&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=hFIeNvnZO4wC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Patron Saint of Liars cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=hFIeNvnZO4wC&amp;dq=intitle:The+Patron+Saint+of+Liars%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=hFIeNvnZO4wC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 1993 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780804111515</guid>
      <dc:date>1993-04-24T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dutch House by Ann Patchett</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=FUMIEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Dutch+House%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Next, dive into TOM LAKE – the breath-taking newest novel from Ann Patchett Lose yourself in the story of a lifetime – the unforgettable Sunday Times bestseller &#39;Patchett leads us to a truth that feels like life rather than literature&#39; Guardian Nominated for the Women&#39;s Prize 2020 A STORY OF TWO SIBLINGS, THEIR CHILDHOOD HOME, AND A PAST THAT THEY CAN&#39;T LET GO. Like swallows, like salmon, we were the helpless captives of our migratory patterns. We pretended that what we had lost was the house, not our mother, not our father. We pretended that what we had lost had been taken from us by the person who still lived inside. In the economic boom following the Second World War, Cyril Conroy&#39;s real estate investments take his family from poverty to enormous wealth. With it he buys the Dutch House, a lavish mansion in the Philadelphia suburbs. Meant as a surprise for his wife, the house sets in motion the undoing of everyone he loves. Danny Conroy grows up in the opulence of the Dutch House. Though his father is distant and his mother is absent, Danny has his beloved sister Maeve: Maeve, with her wall of black hair, her wit, her brilliance. The siblings grow and change as life plays out under the watchful eyes of the house&#39;s former owners, in the frames of their oil paintings. Then one day their father brings home Andrea, a new stepmother. Though they cannot know it, her arrival to the Dutch House sows the seed of the defining loss of Danny and Maeve&#39;s lives: exiled from the house and tossed back into the poverty from which their family rose, Danny and Maeve have only each other to count on. &#39;The best book I&#39;ve read in years&#39; Rosamund Lupton &#39;Her finest novel yet&#39; Sunday Times &#39;The buzz around The Dutch House is totally justified. Her best yet, which is saying something&#39; John Boyne &#39;A masterpiece&#39; Cathy Rentzenbrink &#39;Bliss&#39; Nigella Lawson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2020-11-12&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 353&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781526633934&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=FUMIEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Dutch House cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=FUMIEAAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Dutch+House%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=FUMIEAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781526633934</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-11-12T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth and Beauty by Ann Patchett</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=cjIgAQAAIAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Truth+and+Beauty%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Bestselling author and Orange Prize winner Ann Patchett&#39;s first work of non-fiction is a book about her long friendship with the critically acclaimed, and recently deceased author, Lucy Grealy.It is remarkable for me to remember now that I thought it would be possible to walk away from her, that she might have gone on living, but without me. I know now I never would have had the strength of my convictions. I am living in a world without Lucy. I have no choice about that. If she were alive and I had that choice, I wouldn&#39;t have been able to last without her for a day.&#39;What happens when the person who is your family is someone you aren&#39;t bound to by blood? What happens when the person you promise to love and to honor for the rest of your life is not your lover, but your best friend? In her frank and startlingly intimate first work of nonfiction, Truth &amp; Beauty, Ann Patchett shines light on the little explored world of women&#39;s friendships and shows us what it means to stand together. Ann Patchett and Lucy Grealy met in college in 1981, and after enrolling in the Iowa Writer&#39;s Workshop began a friendship that would be as defining to both of their lives as their work. In her critically&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2004&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 280&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Biography &amp; Autobiography&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=cjIgAQAAIAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Truth and Beauty cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=cjIgAQAAIAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Truth+and+Beauty%2Binauthor:Ann+Patchett&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=cjIgAQAAIAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2004 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">truth-and-beauty-ann-patchett</guid>
      <dc:date>2004-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything I Never Told You by Celeste Ng</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=00GCzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Everything+I+Never+Told+You%2Binauthor:Celeste+Ng&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2019&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 297&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Daughter&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780349144146&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=00GCzgEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Everything I Never Told You cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=00GCzgEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Everything+I+Never+Told+You%2Binauthor:Celeste+Ng&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=00GCzgEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780349144146</guid>
      <dc:date>2019-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Let Him In by Lisa Jewell</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=aBsbEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Don%27t+Let+Him+In%2Binauthor:Lisa+Jewell&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; PREPARE TO BE HOOKED BY THE GRIPPING NEW THRILLER FROM SUNDAY TIMES AND MULTI-MILLION-COPY BESTSELLER LISA JEWELL. &#39;Gripping. Shocking. Masterful.&#39; FREIDA McFADDEN &#39;A thrilling chilling work of genius.&#39; CHRIS WHITAKER &#39;Lisa Jewell is a STONE COLD GENIUS! Don&#39;t Let Him In is a PHENOMENAL achievement&#39; MARIAN KEYES &#39;Utterly absorbing, fiendishly clever and all-consuming&#39; ANDREA MARA ___________ He’s the perfect man. He says he loves you. You think he might even be made for you. Before long he’s moved into your house – and into your heart. And then he leaves for days at a time. You don’t know where he’s gone or who he’s with. And you realise – if you looked back – you’d say to yourself: DON’T LET HIM IN. ___________ Praise for Don&#39;t Let Him In: &#39;A taut, twisty masterclass of a thriller&#39; CLAIRE DOUGLAS &#39;A masterclass in suspense with one of the most chilling, unsettling villains I&#39;ve encountered in a long time&#39; ALEX MICHAELIDES &#39;Hideously plausible and horribly unsettling&#39; HARRIET TYCE ‘A twisty mosaic of a thriller’ GILLIAN McALLISTER &#39;Cancel all plans - this is a read-in-one-sitting book&#39; ALICE FEENEY &#39;I inhaled it within 24 hours. Stunning, shocking, superb.&#39; LIZ NUGENT &#39;Creepy, twisty, and compulsively readable. It hooked me from the first page and never let me go.’ EMILY HENRY &#39;Lisa Jewell, the Queen of sick psychopaths, has outdone herself with Nick, and I am one hundred percent here for it!&#39; TAMMY COHEN &#39;Utterly brilliant&#39; MARK EDWARDS Readers love Don&#39;t Let Him In!: &#39;An absolute masterpiece, with a gripping plot that keeps you hooked from start to finish&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;Gripping, thrilling, jaw dropping, shocking, and twist filled!&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;Obsessed!&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;An absolute page turner&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;Twisty, fast paced, and just an overall enjoyable read&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;Fantastic read. I could not put it down!&#39; 5-star reader review &#39;Very gripping, creepy, suspenseful&#39; 5-star reader review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-07-03&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 314&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781804940273&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=aBsbEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Don’t Let Him In cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=aBsbEQAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Don%27t+Let+Him+In%2Binauthor:Lisa+Jewell&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=aBsbEQAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781804940273</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-07-03T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malibu Rising by Taylor Jenkins Reid</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=aJWJzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Malibu+Rising%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Malibu: August 1983. It&#39;s the day of Nina Riva&#39;s annual end-of-summer party. By midnight the party will be completely out of control. By morning, the Riva mansion will have gone up in flames. But before that first spark in the early hours before dawn, the alcohol will flow, the music will play, and the loves and secrets that shaped this family&#39;s generations will all come rising to the surface&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2021-05-27&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 384&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Families&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781786331526&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=aJWJzQEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Malibu Rising cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=aJWJzQEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Malibu+Rising%2Binauthor:Taylor+Jenkins+Reid&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=aJWJzQEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781786331526</guid>
      <dc:date>2021-05-27T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say You&#39;ll Remember Me by Abby Jimenez</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=C4IG0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Say+You%27ll+Remember+Me&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; &quot;Abby Jimenez has proven time and time again to be one of our must-read writers.&quot;―Cosmopolitan There might be no such a thing as a perfect guy, but Xavier Rush comes disastrously close. A gorgeous veterinarian giving Greek god vibes--all while cuddling a tiny kitten? Immediately yes. That is until Xavier opens his mouth and proves that even sculpted gods can say the absolute wrong thing. Like, really wrong. Of course, there&#39;s nothing Samantha loves more than proving an asshole wrong... . . . unless, of course, he can admit he made a mistake. But after one incredible and seemingly endless date--possibly the best in living history--Samantha is forced to admit the truth, that her family is in crisis and any kind of relationship would be impossible. Samantha begs Xavier to forget her. To remember their night together as a perfect moment, as crushing as that may be. Only no amount of distance or time is nearly enough to forget that something between them. And the only thing better than one single perfect memory is to make a life--and even a love--worth remembering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2025-04&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781538774168&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=C4IG0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Say You&#39;ll Remember Me cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=C4IG0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Say+You%27ll+Remember+Me&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=C4IG0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781538774168</guid>
      <dc:date>2025-04-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach Read by Emily Henry</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=lxGuDwAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; FROM THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF PEOPLE WE MEET ON VACATION AND BOOK LOVERS! A romance writer who no longer believes in love and a literary writer stuck in a rut engage in a summer-long challenge that may just upend everything they believe about happily ever afters. Augustus Everett is an acclaimed author of literary fiction. January Andrews writes bestselling romance. When she pens a happily ever after, he kills off his entire cast. They’re polar opposites. In fact, the only thing they have in common is that for the next three months, they&#39;re living in neighboring beach houses, broke, and bogged down with writer&#39;s block. Until, one hazy evening, one thing leads to another and they strike a deal designed to force them out of their creative ruts: Augustus will spend the summer writing something happy, and January will pen the next Great American Novel. She’ll take him on field trips worthy of any rom-com montage, and he’ll take her to interview surviving members of a backwoods death cult (obviously). Everyone will finish a book and no one will fall in love. Really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2020-05-19&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 401&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781984806741&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lxGuDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Beach Read cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=lxGuDwAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=lxGuDwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781984806741</guid>
      <dc:date>2020-05-19T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emily Henry 4 Books Collection Set: Book Lovers, Beach Read, People We Meet on Vacation &amp; Happy Place by Emily Henry</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Booklovers%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2022-04-13&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9798998881114&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Emily Henry 4 Books Collection Set: Book Lovers, Beach Read, People We Meet on Vacation &amp; Happy Place cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Booklovers%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=ECFf0QEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798998881114</guid>
      <dc:date>2022-04-13T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You and Me on Vacation by Emily Henry</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=T6r7DwAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+People+You+Meet+on+Vacation%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; SET TO BE A MAJOR NETFLIX RELEASE STARRING EMILY BADER AND TOM BLYTH! Two friends. Ten trips. Their last chance to fall in love... ------ &#39;One of my favourite authors&#39; Colleen Hoover, It Ends With Us &#39;A gorgeous romance&#39; Beth O&#39;Leary, The No-Show &#39;Loveable characters, hilarious wit and steamy sexual chemistry&#39; Laura Jane Williams, Our Stop *Also known as People We Meet On Vacation* 12 YEARS AGO: Poppy and Alex meet. They hate each other, and are pretty confident they&#39;ll never speak again. 11 YEARS AGO: They&#39;re forced to share a ride home from college and by the end of it a friendship is formed. And a pact: every year, one vacation together. 10 YEARS AGO: Alex discovers his fear of flying on the way to Vancouver. Poppy holds his hand the whole way. 7 YEARS AGO: They get far too drunk and narrowly avoid getting matching tattoos in New Orleans. 2 YEARS AGO: It all goes wrong. THIS YEAR: Poppy asks Alex to join her on one last trip. A trip that will determine the rest of their lives. People We Meet On Vacation is a New York Times bestselling love story for fans of When Harry Met Sally, One Day and Casey McQuiston. Get ready to travel the world, snort with laughter and - most of all - lose your heart to Poppy and Alex. ** Previously published under the title You and Me on Vacation ** ------ &#39;Our generation&#39;s answer to Nora Ephron&#39; Sophie Cousens, This Time Next Year &#39;So warm and funny&#39; Paige Toon, The Minute I Saw You &#39;The hottest book of the summer - the pages simply sizzle!&#39; Josie Silver, One Night on the Island &#39;Emily Henry is my newest automatic-buy author . . . a heartfelt, funny, tender escape that you wish could last forever&#39; Jodi Picoult, Wish You Were Here &#39;A compulsively readable book full of sparkling wit, dazzling prose and a romance that grabbed me by the heart and wouldn&#39;t let me go&#39; Abby Jiminez, Part of Your World &#39;Funny, and seriously sizzling&#39; BEST &#39;If whipcrack banter and sexual tension is your catnip, you&#39;ll adore this book&#39; Sally Thorne, The Hating Game &#39;What an absolute flipping triumph of a novel!!! I LOVED it &#39; Emma Cooper, It Was Always You Emily Henry, Sunday Times bestseller, May 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2021-05-11&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 320&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780241992241&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=T6r7DwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;You and Me on Vacation cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=T6r7DwAAQBAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+People+You+Meet+on+Vacation%2Binauthor:Emily+Henry&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=T6r7DwAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780241992241</guid>
      <dc:date>2021-05-11T00:00:00+10:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last One Out Wins by S. Lael Brainard</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=cAuyAAAAIAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Last+Lie+Wins&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This paper examines the effect of government intervention on the order and timing of firm exit in an international industry with fixed costs and declined demand. A dynamic inconsistency problem arises when the government is unable to precommit to a path of policy: it always intervenes to prolong the viability of the firm located in its market, even when the firm&#39;s survival is not the socially optimal outcome. The effect of tariff intervention is in all cases to terminate market operation prematurely, and in many cases to reverse the order of firm exit. Intervention in the absence of precommittment is never first best, and actually reduces welfare relative to the free market equilibrium when the differential between firms&#39; fixed costs is large.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 1990&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 70&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Competition, International&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=cAuyAAAAIAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Last One Out Wins cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=cAuyAAAAIAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Last+Lie+Wins&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=cAuyAAAAIAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 1990 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">last-one-out-wins-s.-lael-brainard</guid>
      <dc:date>1990-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen for the Lie by Amy Tintera</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=P5S9EAAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; A New York Times Bestseller * A Good Morning America Book Club Pick * An NPR Best Book of the Year * A Washington Post Best Thriller of 2024 &quot;A world-class whodunit.&quot; —Stephen King “An extremely successful high-wire act, balancing between dark comedy and darker thrills.” —Alex Michaelides, #1 New York Times bestselling author “Laugh-out-loud funny, thrilling and twisty...” —Liane Moriarty, #1 New York Times bestselling author What if you thought you murdered your best friend? And if everyone else thought so too? And what if the truth doesn&#39;t matter? After Lucy is found wandering the streets, covered in her best friend Savvy’s blood, everyone thinks she is a murderer. Lucy and Savvy were the golden girls of their small Texas town: pretty, smart, and enviable. Lucy married a dream guy with a big ring and an even bigger new home. Savvy was the social butterfly loved by all, and if you believe the rumors, especially popular with the men in town. It’s been years since that horrible night, a night Lucy can’t remember anything about, and she has since moved to LA and started a new life. But now the phenomenally huge hit true crime podcast &quot;Listen for the Lie,&quot; and its too-good looking host Ben Owens, have decided to investigate Savvy’s murder for the show’s second season. Lucy is forced to return to the place she vowed never to set foot in again to solve her friend’s murder, even if she is the one that did it. The truth is out there, if we just listen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024-03-05&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 317&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9781250880321&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=P5S9EAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Listen for the Lie cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=P5S9EAAAQBAJ&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=P5S9EAAAQBAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9781250880321</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-03-05T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Author&#39;s Guide to Murder by Beatriz/ Willig Lauren/ White Williams (Karen)</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=PK0Z0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Author%E2%80%99s+Guide+to+Murder&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2024&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=PK0Z0QEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Author%E2%80%99s+Guide+to+Murder&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">the-author&#39;s-guide-to-murder-beatriz/-willig-lauren/-white-williams-(karen)</guid>
      <dc:date>2024-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mother-Daughter Book Club Rev Ed. by Shireen Dodson</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=7QOr0AEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Mother-Daughter+Book+Club&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Newly revised and updated! The tenth anniversary edition of the inspirational book that has brought countless mothers and daughters closer together! The Mother-Daughter Book Club is the story of a group of mothers and their daughters, and how their relationships were strengthened and changed by starting a monthly reading club. But it is also a practical step-by-step guide—filled with stories, anecdotes, and reading lists—that will inspire parents to start reading clubs of their own. Shireen Dodson&#39;s message is a powerful one: Reading, learning, and sharing ideas can help nourish a daughter&#39;s confidence, strength, spirit, and independence. A reading club offers a mother the opportunity to enjoy her daughter&#39;s burgeoning mind as she moves toward womanhood. The Mother-Daughter Book Club is not merely about books. It is about mothers and daughters, girls and women, and how reading and talking enriches our relationships with one another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2007-03-13&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Family &amp; Relationships&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780060890346&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7QOr0AEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Mother-Daughter Book Club Rev Ed. cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=7QOr0AEACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Mother-Daughter+Book+Club&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=7QOr0AEACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2007 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780060890346</guid>
      <dc:date>2007-03-13T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dear Mr. Henshaw by Beverly Cleary</title>
      <link>https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=FBTUeGolvsIC&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Newbery Medal Winner * Teachers’ Top 100 Books for Children * ALA Notable Children’s Book Beverly Cleary’s timeless Newbery Medal-winning book explores difficult topics like divorce, insecurity, and bullying through the thoughts and emotions of a sixth-grade boy as he writes to his favorite author, Boyd Henshaw. After his parents separate, Leigh Botts moves to a new town with his mother. Struggling to make friends and deal with his anger toward his absent father, Leigh loses himself in a class assignment in which he must write to his favorite author. When Mr. Henshaw responds, the two form an unexpected friendship that will change Leigh’s life forever. From the beloved author of the Henry Huggins, Ramona Quimby, and Ralph S. Mouse series comes an epistolary novel about how to navigate and heal from life’s growing pains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2009-10-06&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 164&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Juvenile Fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780061972157&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=FBTUeGolvsIC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;Dear Mr. Henshaw cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/books/details?id=FBTUeGolvsIC&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=FBTUeGolvsIC&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;edge=curl&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780061972157</guid>
      <dc:date>2009-10-06T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Red House Mystery by Alan Alexander Milne</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=LMZSPwAACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Red+House+Mystery%2Binauthor:A.+A.+Milne&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; Far from the gentle slopes of the Hundred Acre Wood lies The Red House, where secret passages, uninvited guests, a sinister valet and a puzzling murder lay the foundations for a classic crime caper. And when the local police prove baffled, it is up to a guest at a local inn to appoint himself &#39;Sherlock Holmes&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 2009&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Classical fiction&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780099521273&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://books.google.com/books/content?id=LMZSPwAACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api&quot; alt=&quot;The Red House Mystery cover&quot; style=&quot;max-width: 200px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=LMZSPwAACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:The+Red+House+Mystery%2Binauthor:A.+A.+Milne&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://books.google.com/books/content?id=LMZSPwAACAAJ&amp;printsec=frontcover&amp;img=1&amp;zoom=1&amp;source=gbs_api"
        length="0"
        type="image/jpeg"/>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780099521273</guid>
      <dc:date>2009-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strangers on a Train by Patricia Highsmith</title>
      <link>http://books.google.com/books?id=3kNhPwAACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Strangers+on+a+Train%2Binauthor:Patricia+Highsmith&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; One of a series designed as an introduction to literature. It is graded into six levels, and each book contains an introduction and exercises. It is designed for students of English as a foreign or as a second language, and for reluctant readers. This is a chilling psychological thriller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Details:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Published: 1995&lt;br/&gt;Pages: 57&lt;br/&gt;Categories: Insanity (Law)&lt;br/&gt;ISBN: 9780140814880&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=3kNhPwAACAAJ&amp;dq=intitle:Strangers+on+a+Train%2Binauthor:Patricia+Highsmith&amp;hl=&amp;source=gbs_api&quot;&gt;View on Google Books&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 1995 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9780140814880</guid>
      <dc:date>1995-01-01T00:00:00+11:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2025-08-14T10:11:44+10:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>